Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: Jun 5, 2023

Fellow Insights, Inc. (“Fellow”) takes your privacy very seriously. We have created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to outline how we collect, use and disclose Personal Data from Users of our website and web-application (the “Platform”), located at [**https://fellow.app**](https://fellow.app/) (“Site”), our Apps (e.g. Fellow for iOS/Android, Fellow for Mac/Windows, Fellow Browser Extension), and our Communications Platform Apps (e.g. Fellow for Slack, Fellow for MS Teams, etc…) and the related services described in our Terms of Use (collectively, the “Services”).

Please review the following text to understand our protocol with regards to Personal Data and how we treat it. By visiting [**https://fellow.app**](https://fellow.app/), signing up for our Platform, installing any of our Apps, or using our Communications Platform Apps, installing any of our you are providing your acceptance and consent to practices outlined here.

Background Information
----------------------

When we refer to “Users”, we are referring to both individual users (“Individual Users”) and Organizational users that hold an Account on the Site or have installed our Bots. The Services allow Users the opportunity to track and take notes on 1:1s and other meetings, exchange feedback, track goals/priorities and other items as they relate to working together. In the event that an Organization purchases a subscription to the Services, they will have access to aggregate reporting relating to usage of the Services by Users and other related analytics associated with their Organization. By default, Organizations will not have access to the content of Notes or Feedback Messages of Users who create this content. If an Organization’s policies require access to this data, then Fellow will comply. It is your responsibility to read and understand your Organization’s internal privacy policies.

Definitions
-----------

Terms utilized in this Privacy Policy have meanings as defined below:

1. “Notes” refers to any content written in relation to interactions that Users have with other Users (whether in a 1:1 or group setting).
2. “Feedback Messages” include the related messages that are exchanged by Users in the process of requesting or giving feedback.
3. “Organization” refers to the entity that entered into a subscription agreement with Fellow and that you provided to us when you created an Account with Fellow (or that we otherwise retrieve during the signup process). The Organization will generally be your employer, or a subsection of your employer (i.e. department).
4. “Personal Data” means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession), and any information about the individual associated with that information.
5. “Work Network” is the group of employees, contractors or other authorized Users at your Organization.

Contacting Fellow
-----------------

If you have questions or concerns about what is described here in our Privacy Policy or you have other communications including the reporting of violations that should be brought to our attention, you may contact us below:

Fellow Insights, Inc.  
To: Privacy Department  
532 Montréal Rd #275, Ottawa, ON K1K 4R4  
**privacy@fellow.app**

Children under 13
-----------------

Fellow does not knowingly offer its Services to children who are under 13 years of age. If we become aware of usage of its services by individuals in this age group, we will attempt to delete all related information immediately. If you have any information related to such usage, please report it to us at **privacy@fellow.app**

General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliance
----------------------------------------------------

For residents of the European Economic Area, Fellow generally processes Personal Data in order to fulfill contracts we have with the Organizations that are our customers and Users, as well as to pursue our legitimate business interests as set out in this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, Fellow will obtain consent from an Individual User in respect of processing of Personal Data.

When we process data on behalf of Organizations under an agreement with that Organization, Fellow is acting as the “data processor” and the Organization is the “data controller”.

Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) have certain data protection rights under applicable laws (including under the GDPR), including the right to request access to, obtain, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. Individual Users who wish to exercise these rights, should contact Fellow using the contact information. In circumstances where Fellow is a data processor and the Organization is the data controller, Individuals may be required to contact the Organization to avail themselves of such rights.

Information collected from Users will be processed by us and some of our affiliate services and service providers (“Sub-Processors”). A list of our current Sub-Processors is available [**here**](https://www.fellow.app/fellow-app-sub-processors/). We will take reasonably necessary steps, including contractual measures and other legal requirements, to ensure that your Personal Data is dealt with the same level of caution and care as described in this Privacy Policy.

Data transferred from the European Economic Area to Fellow or a Sub-Processor shall be in accordance with approved international transfer mechanisms under applicable law.

Security
--------

We take security seriously and use appropriate technical measures corresponding to the types of Personal Data we store, and the risks associated with processing such data. In the event of a data breach we will contact those affected as well as any applicable regulators as required by law. You can learn more about Fellow’s security and compliance practices [**here**](https://help.fellow.app/en/articles/4302231-security-compliance).

Types of Data We Collect
------------------------

When using our Services, we collect information from you – some of which is considered “Personal Data” and can be used to identify you, and some of which is “Anonymous Data” which is not linked to any identifiable individual. In the following sections, we will outline the details of what we collect and how:

### Information You Provide

When you sign up, we create an account for you on our servers (“Account”) to access our Services. We will store information such as your first name, last name, job title, department and email address.

Fellow’s primary objective is to help you manage your work relationships through the logging of discussions, feedback, goals/priorities and more with others that you work with (whether individually or in groups). Fellow also offers smart suggestions on what actions you may want to take in order to optimize these relationships (for example, “you should [ask for feedback](https://fellow.app/blog/feedback/how-to-ask-for-feedback-in-a-professional-setting/) from someone in particular”). In order to provide such suggestions, we need to compute a “work-graph” that will give us insights into the people that you work with and how often you work with them. In order to offer these Services, we require access to the following information:

* Calendar: We access data about the events that you participate in such as organizer, title, attendees and optional attendees (names and emails), date, time, duration, calendar resources (meeting rooms) and recurrence of events.

Once you sign up, we may ask you more information including your job title, department, who your manager is and whether you have a 1on1 with this manager and which calendar event this corresponds to. We also provide the opportunity for you to invite other individuals into the platform so that you may collaborate with them (in order to invite others, we may ask you for some further information about those Users including their name, email address and reporting relationship with you).

Your main interactions with Fellow will either directly through our Platform, one of our communications platform apps, or via one of our integrations.. Users on the system will be able to collaborate on notes in relation to 1:1 and group meetings, goals/priorities and request feedback from one another and provide feedback to each other. The content created by these Users will be stored and accessible through the Services. This information is by default only accessible to Users who were part of the interactions and is not accessible by managers of the company (unless those that were part of the feedback interactions explicitly share such feedback with others such as managers). Metadata about the interactions (such as stats on usage) will be available to managers. The only exception to this rule will be if the policies of the Organization require us to share this information upon request from the Organization.

### Information Collected through Systems

#### Servers

Our servers (hosted by Amazon Web Services) collect information including the type of browser and O/S you use, your IP Address, domain name and the timing / duration of your visit to our Site. This information is collected to make our Services more useful to you.

#### Logs

We record some information from your interactions with our Services automatically in our logs. This data includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. This information is used to analyze trends and usage patterns all in an effort to better tailor our Services to your needs.

#### Cookies

Fellow and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track Users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages on our Websites, or register for the Services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Fellow Services when you visit. Fellow keeps track of the pages you visit within Fellow, in order to determine what portion of the Fellow Services is the most popular or most used. This data is used to deliver customized content and promotions within the Fellow Services to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

#### Pixel Tags

We use “Clear Gifs” also known as “Pixel Tags” similar to cookies to track the usage of our Services by Users. These “Clear Gifs” are effectively transparent images that allow us to glean some information about said usage. An example common use case is to use this technology to understand the open-rate of emails that we send to you. Ultimately, like cookies, we use this tool as another method to customize our offerings for our customers.

#### Analytics Software and Advertising Platforms

We use some analytics services from third party vendors such as Google Analytics in order to analyze usage of our Services. These services utilize information that they retrieve from cookies on our Web Application or other information that we send them directly to provide us with aggregated analytics that we can use to perform our analysis. These analytics services will have their own privacy policies and terms of use. By using our Services, you are agreeing to the processing of this data by such analytics services.

We participate in network advertising programs that display advertising about our services on other unaffiliated websites. We use third party social media platforms (e.g. Facebook, Linkedin, etc.) to show you [customized social media ads and interest-based ads](https://fellow.app/privacy-policy/advertising-definitions/).

### Information Collected from Others

By connecting your Calendar as mentioned earlier in this document, we will be able to determine who works with whom with your organization so as to offer you smart suggestions on how to improve your working relationships with people in your network, as well as allow the ability to take notes on each of your meetings.

Below we list the types of data we collect from the various Fellow apps for the communications platforms that we support. Each is only applicable if you or your organization has installed the respective app on the third party platform.

* **Fellow for Slack**: Information about the users in your Slack account and the individuals you interact with most often. In particular, if Fellow for Slack is connected: Avatars, Team Names, Channel Membership, Communications within the @Fellow bot and metadata derived from such communications and OAuth Tokens. We do NOT request access to the content of your direct messages (“DMs”) or the content of your private channels.
* **Fellow for Microsoft Teams**: Information about the users in your Teams account and the individuals you interact with most often. In particular, if Fellow for Microsoft Teams is connected: Avatars, Team Names, Team Memberships, Communications within the @Fellow bot, and metadata derived from such communications and OAuth Tokens. We do NOT request access to the content of your chat messages (“DMs”) or the content of your private channels.
* **Fellow for Zoom:** Information about you, and information about your meetings. In particular, if Fellow for Zoom is connected: Meeting titles and Times, Meeting recording links, and your user information (IDs and email addresses). We do NOT have any access to the content of your recordings (whether local or on Zoom Cloud).
* **Fellow for Zoom Chat:** Information about you, and individuals with whom you interact with most often. In particular, if Fellow for Zoom Chat is connected: Avatars, Team names, Channel memberships, Communications with the Fellow bot, and metadata derived from such communications and OAuth Tokens.  We do NOT request access to the content of your chat messages (“DMs”) or the content of your private channels.

Note that the Fellow for Microsoft Teams app is enabled by the Microsoft Bot Framework. The Microsoft Bot Framework is a set of web-services that enable intelligent services and connections using conversation channels you authorize. As a service provider, Microsoft will transmit content you provide to our bot/service in order to enable the service. For more information about Microsoft privacy policies please see their privacy statement here: [**http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=521839**](https://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkId=521839). In addition, your interactions with this bot/service are also subject to the conversational channel’s applicable terms of use, privacy and data collection policies. To report abuse when using a bot that uses the Microsoft Bot Framework to Microsoft, please visit the Microsoft Bot Framework website at [https://www.botframework.com](https://www.botframework.com/) and use the “Report Abuse” link in the menu to contact Microsoft.

### Information Collected from Your Organization

If your Organization becomes a customer of ours, we will create accounts for your usage of our Services. We may obtain from your Organization information about you such as your name, email address, title, department and reporting relationships.

### Prospective Customers

We collect names, email addresses and other business contact information about individuals who represent our customers as well as individuals who we consider to be prospective customers and business partners (“Prospects”). We use the information to contact Prospects with information about Fellow products and services.

Use of Your Personal Data
-------------------------

### General Use

In general, we use the Personal Data we have about you to offer you a more tailored experience and to respond to any requests you send us in a more comprehensive fashion. We use this data in the following ways:

* Allow for the creation of your account.
* Identify you on our system and keep track of the Work Network you are involved in.
* Improve the Services that we offer you and provide a more tailored experience.
* Respond to the requests that you send us.
* Send you messages (via our Communications Bots, and Email and our Web Application) that relate to your usage of our system or security and administrative messages.
* Send you smart suggestions and feedback received from others in your Work Network.
* Send you communication requests for the purpose of improving our Services (i.e. request for phone call, completion of a survey).
* Send marketing related messages to our Services with your consent (from which you will be able to unsubscribe).
* To Send you other notifications that relate to your usage of the system (for example, the fact that you have some pending feedback requests or if you have some unviewed feedback).

### Anonymous Data

We use anonymized data retrieved from our database (i.e. where personally identifiable information has been obfuscated) in order to create analytics that will help us surmise how to improve our Service. Some of the reports created with this anonymized data may be shared with your Organization so that they can understand the overall usage of our product by their employees/constituents.

Disclosure of Personal Information
----------------------------------

Disclosures of your Personal Data are described as below

### Designated 3rd Parties

We will share your Personal Data with parties that you have already consented to share information with such as your Organization and those in your Work Network. For example, feedback that you exchange with other Users in your Work Network will be viewed by them.

### Third Party Service Providers

We use a set of third parties as part of our system in order to offer you the Services that we do. Examples include analytics services (as described previously) and email service providers. Service Providers who process Personal Data on our behalf are considered Sub-Processors.

#### Service Providers related to Fellow’s AI services

We use a set of third parties in order to offer you Artificial Intelligence (AI) Services such as processing intent, smart suggestions for your meetings, meeting recording services, transcription services, summarization, content creation, editing, question answering, intelligent search, etc…

The transfer of your organizations’ data to AI-related third party service providers can be controlled by administrators in your organization with a toggle in your Workspace settings in the Platform (Workspace Settings -> Security -> Artificial Intelligence). When this toggle is disabled, any features which rely on these third-party AI providers will also be disabled.  When the toggle is enabled, certain additional features will be available for your account that rely on these services (exclusively on a per-use basis of the respective features, not via background transfers). Any such features are appropriately decorated within the Platform with similar iconography.

A full list of our sub-processors, including our AI sub-processors is available [**here**](https://www.fellow.app/fellow-app-sub-processors/).

### Disclosure to Organization

In the event that your Organization becomes a customer of our Services, we will share information about your account related to usage statistics (such as number of feedback exchanges and with whom these exchanges happened) but will not share the content of the feedback exchanged. Your organization may have specific policies in place regarding how Personal Data is shared to which we will have to comply.

### Business Transfers

If our business (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired by a third party, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Data may be made available or otherwise transferred to the new controlling entity, where permitted under applicable law.

### Other

In certain situations, we may receive a demand to disclose Personal Data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Fellow may disclose your Personal Data (a) to any governmental authority as part of an investigation to determine our compliance with any applicable law, rule, or regulation (including privacy laws, rules, and regulations), (b) in response to a court order, subpoena, discovery request, or other lawful judicial or administrative proceeding, (c) as otherwise required under any applicable law, rule, or regulation, and (d) in good faith, to defend the rights or property of Fellow and other Users and (e) if Fellow is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Data, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Data.

Third Party Websites
--------------------

Our Websites provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.

Sensitive Personal Data
-----------------------

If you provide us with sensitive information in the course of interacting with the system, we will only use sensitive information for the purpose of storing and processing it as part of our Services. Sensitive information may include information about you such as racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, political affiliation, sexual preferences and criminal records, as well as health and genetic information about you. If you do not consent to the processing and storing of your sensitive information, it is therefore important that it not be submitted to us in the course of your usage.

Options Considering Personal Data
---------------------------------

We describe some of the changes and options available to you on Personal Data below:

### Email Communications

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our emails, or by sending us an email at **privacy@fellow.app**. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with us or the Services.

### Cookies

If you do not want to accept Cookies from our site, you may change your browser settings to not accept cookies. If you do not accept these cookies, you may not be able to use our Site and Services to the fullest extent.

### Interest-Based Advertising

You can opt-out of network advertising programs that track your activities across multiple websites to deliver personalized advertising content to you. Please visit:

* Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada Opt-Out Page: [http://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising](http://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising)
* NAI Opt-Out Page: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
* Ad Choices Opt-Out Page: [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

These websites provide tools that identify member companies that have placed cookies on your browser and provide tools to allow you to opt-out of those cookies. Please note that if you opt-out you may still receive online advertising from Fellow on other websites or applications; however, these advertisements will not be displayed to you based on your interests. Please also note that deleting browser cookies can remove your opt-out preferences, so you should use these tools periodically to ensure that your preferences are up-to-date.

### Customized Social Media Ads

To opt-out of customized social media ads, adjust your social advertising settings (for example, through the settings of your Facebook profile), or use the links provided in the ad itself.

### Access, Modification or Deletion of Your Data

You may contact us at **privacy@fellow.app** in order to request a copy, change or delete any Personal Data that we have on file for your Account. Please note that feedback exchanged cannot be deleted as it involves more than one party. As an Organizational customer, you may request the deletion of your entire Account (and all individual Users within that account). We will delete this information within 15 days of your request. Your information may stay on our backup servers for up to an additional 30 days but will no longer be present thereafter.

Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) have additional data protection rights under applicable laws (including under the General Data Protection Regulation), including the right to request access to, obtain, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. Individual Users who wish to exercise these rights, should contact Fellow using the contact information. In circumstances where Fellow is a data processor and the Organization is the data controller, Individuals may be required to contact the Organization to avail themselves of such rights.

### Retention

We retain Personal Data that you provide us as long as we consider it necessary for the purpose it was collected, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, and then we securely delete the information. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described above. If a customer terminates its use of the Services, we will, unless legally prohibited, delete all customer information, including your Personal Data, from the Services.

Periodic Updates to Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. In the event of an update, we will post the new policy at [https://fellow.app/privacy-policy](https://fellow.app/privacy-policy) and update the “Last Updated” date above. Please check this page regularly for updates.
